Fathin **Dosunmu**

Address Tallinn, Estonia, 12611

Phone 372-536-5309

E-mail Fathindos.fd@gmail.com

LinkedIn LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/fathindos

WWW WWW: https://fato07.github.io/home

WWW https://leetcode.com/fathindos/

Web developer that learns through trial and error. Detailed understanding of complex, up-to-date programming languages and considerations. Experience designing and developing sites from concept to roll out. Even though I love to get my work done in the best way, I have a great sense of humour. Thorough grasp of react js and firebase contributes to generating custom script for specific organisational needs

Skills

Web Security	Good
Fireabse	Excellent
Google Cloud API	
React js	Excellent
C#	Excellent
ASP.net	Very Good
	Very Good
Can adapt to new tools and frameworks depending on task to be fufilled	Excellent
Javascript	Excellent
Restful API	Excellent
Docker	Good
Linux	
Azure Web services	Very Good
	Good

Work History

Kuehne+nagel, Tallinn, Estonia

Key Responsibilities

- Main focus on Redux and its implementations in large scale applications.
- Managed full-cycle design tasks, handling all phases from conception to completion while maintaining guidelines throughout.
- Worked in Agile-driven environment to effectively maintain project timelines and utilize available resources.

2021-02 - 2021-05 Web Developer

Fundamental Secrets, Florida, United Sates

Key Responsibilities

- Responsible for developing website product used by approximately 600 + users
- Planned website development, converting ideas into features with HTML, JavaScript, React-js and Firebase
- Implemented payment gateways with Paypal and Stripe.
- Oversaw front-end with mainly React-js and back-end development with mainly firebase.
- Multitasked across multiple functions and ideas to generate project results and meet deadlines.
- Engaged with marketing officer to plan, optimise and repair issues as work environment was changing rapidly.
- Product built and was responsible for: https://fundamentalsecrets.web.app/

2020-06 - 2020-08 Test Developer Intern

Ericsson, Tallinn, Estonia

Key Responsibilities

- Prepared Software For Testing 5G units before Production.
- Optimised existing code for software Tool within Ericsson's Tech Stack. (C#, SQL and MDX).
- Prepared and Implemented Test criteria and TestPlan in Test Programs for HighBand Products.

Education

2020-09 - Current Master of Science: Cyber Security

Taltech - Tallinn, Estonia

Https://www.taltech.ee/en/cyber-msc

2017-09 - 2020-06 Bachelor of Science: Integrated Engineering

Taltech - Tallinn, Estonia

Https://www.taltech.ee/en/integrated-engineering.

Hobby Projects

- Built a clone of whatsApp Chat. A User can signln, Post a chat in a chat room and chat with other users: https://whatsapp-clone-bd456.web.app/ (React js and Firebase for development)
- Currently developing a website to track activities and events of different users.
 (It is not hosted yet, but its code is available on github: Https://github.com/Fato07/Reactivities.git).
- A User can create, edit or delete an event. follow other users, unfollow other users, chat with other users, update profile pictures, upload images, add comments to posts etc. The WebApp is Developed based on a API Web architecture that interacts with react.js as the front end service for client side and ASP.NET for server side. Command Query Responsibility Segregation (CQRS) Pattern used for dataBase Handling on server side. Mobx for managing Application State on front end side. SignalR for realTime chatting.